...won't... forgive... you... though!
Those people... I can use them.
That's all you are to us, decoys. Nothing more.
They disappeared! Both of them disappeared!
A-A woman dressed in work clothes who sat over there...
It's already caught up!
Rail Tracer!
そうか 無事に到着したのか
I see. So it has arrived safely?
It didn't arrive so safely, apparently...
それが あまり
無事ではなかったようで
どういうことだ?
What do you mean?
フライングプツシ一フッ 卜号は
機関車だけでな<
Besides the locomotive, it appears all of the passenger cars were replaced as well.
客車ごと代車に
替えられたそうです
状況は把握できているのか ?
Do you know about the circumstances?
Just bits and pieces...
断片的には…
ネブラ社が
情報統制に動い乙いるので
The Nebula Company is restricting information, so it's hard to grasp the whole picture,
なかなか全体像が
把握できないのですが
相当の事件であることは
間違いありません
but it was definitely a large incident.
かなりの乗客力ヾ
死てしているようです
Apparently, quite a few passengers have died.
フライングプツシ一フツ 卜には
確か彼女が乗っていたね
Wasn't that girl riding on board the Flying Pussyfoot?
はい
Yes.
Let's await her report first.
まずは彼女の報告を待つとしようか
何を見 何を聞き 何を知つたのか
What she saw, what she heard, what she got to know...
もぅ見えているようですが…
I can see her already, though.
レイチ工ル君 よく帰つてきたね
Rachel-kun,
I'm glad to see you got back home safely.
フライングプツシ一フッ 卜号に
関しては
We only received horrible information about the Flying Pussyfoot,
よろし<ない情報ばかりが
入つてきていたから とても心配したよ
so I was very worried about you.
As the director of Daily Days, I feel honored to have someone like you working for us.
君のような部下が持てたことを
デイリ一デイズ社長として誇りに思う
ありがとうございます
Thank you.
また無賃乗車ですか?
Did you hitch a free ride again?
そうですが それが何か ?
Yes, that's right. Is there something wrong with that?
二コラス君 レイ チ工丿し君の
足のケガを見ても
Nicholas-kun,
just from looking at Rachel-kun's leg injury, you should realize that the circumstances aren't normal,
ただならぬ状況であることは明白だ
軽ロは つつしみたまえ
so keep your silly jokes to yourself.
失礼いたしましたぁ
I apologize for my rudeness.
さて レイチ工ル君
Well now, Rachel-kun.
本当なら君には たっぷりと静養を
取つてもらいたいところなのだが
I'd really like you to take some rest now. However...
我々は情報屋だ
早速 報告を頼むよ
We are an information shop.
So let's hear your report...
フライングプツシ一フッ 卜号で
何が起こったのか
about what happened on board the Flying Pussyfoot.
私に分かるのは私が見た範囲の
ことでしかありませんが…
I only know about the things I could see, though...
それで構わない
教えて<れたまえ
That's all right.
Tell me. Who were those black-suited people, and who were those white-suited people?
黒服の連中が何者なのか
白服の連中が何者なのか…
社長 私よりお詳しいようですね…
Director, it looks like you know more than me.
And... who or what is Rail Tracer?
そして レイ丿し卜レ一サ一とは
何者なのか…
レイ丿し卜レ一サ一…
Rail... Tracer...
W-What is Rail Tracer?
レ… レイ丿し卜レ一サ一つて?
なあ~んだ…
ジヤグジ一は知らないのかあ?
What? You don't know, Jacuzzi?
レイル卜レ一サ一つてのはなぁ一一
Rail Tracer is...
Now that you mention it,
そういえば食堂車で乗客が
そんな話をしていたような…
I vaguely remember some people in the dining car talking about it...
The one lurking in the shadows of the railroad.
線路の影をなぞるもの…
伝説の怪物だ
A legendary monster.
'怪物‥
Monster?
Yes, a monster.
そう 怪物だ
あれが果たしてそうなのかは
分かりませんが…
I don't know whether it's true or not, but...
フライングプツシ一フツ卜には
確かに怪物が乗つていました
there was definitely a monster riding on board the Flying Pussyfoot.
真つ赤で… 残酷な怪物が
A deep-red, cruel monster was...
壷かしいって マジで
信じられねえって
This is strange, really!
I can't believe it!
いや マジで
何で ここ血の海なのよぉ
Really!
Why is there a sea of blood?
おかしくねえ ? むしろすごくねえ ?
You don't think that's strange?
I mean, isn't it amazing?!
何をどうやつたら
こんな汚い殺し方できんのよ
What method could you use to kill someone in such a filthy manner?!
なあなあなあ よお
Hey, hey, hey!
この顔面ない奴つて あれか
デユ一ンの奴か?
This guy without a face, is it him?
It might just be Dune.
すつげ一な おい
三イラ取りが三イラになつてるよ
This is amazing!
The hunter became the hunted!
ああっ… って一か 誰だよ
デユ一ンの奴 殺したの!?
By the way, who was it that killed Dune?!
敲き取つてやろうにも
相手が分かんなきゃ話にならねえ
It's hard to take revenge if you don't know who did it!
あああぁあああぁ…
デユ一ンはなんて
かわいそうな奴なんだろお…
What a poor fellow Dune is...
To think his friends can't take revenge for him...
仲間に敵も
取つてもらえねえたあな
Well then, the all-important rescue method...
さて… 肝心の助かる方法だが…
この話を聞いた奴は
皆すぐに死んでしまいました
Those who heard this story all died soon after.
助かる方法は
ーつもありませんでしたとさつ !
There was not one rescue method!
助かる方法はあるさ…
Sure there is a rescue method!
やられる前に やることだ!
You just have to kill before you get killed.
ま 待て 待つてくれ
W-Wait! Wait a bit!
イヤだね
Not a chance.
そうそう 俺の話の続きだけどな
Ah, right. The continuation of my story...
レイ丿し卜レ一サ一カヾ
来ないようにする方法は
You have to believe this story in order for Rail Tracer not to come,
今の話を信じること
来ちまった場合は
朝巳が昇るまで逃げることだ
and if he's come already, you have to flee before the sun rises.
Well, it's already too late, though.
ま もう遅いけどな
お前らにとってのレイル卜レ一サ一は
確実に現れる
He who is Rail Tracer will definitely appear.
He will awaken when I fire this gun.
この銃声で目を覚ます
お前の死によって目を覚ます
He will awaken as a result of your death.
Die, you sacrificial lamb.
死ねよ 生け藝
何だ こりや
What's going on here?
Who are you?
お前は誰だ ?
え? ちよっと待つて下さいよ
私は怪しい者じゃありませんよ
Wait a little, please.
I'm no one suspicious.
この列車に車掌は
俺たち2人しか乗つてないはずだ
He and I ought to be the only conductors on board this train.
お前は誰だ
Who are you?
ちよつと その物騒な物
しまつて下さいよ
Please put that dangerous thing away.
こんな状況で どうしてそんなに
余裕でいられる?
How can you remain so calm under these circumstances?
Who are you? What is your goal?
お前は誰だ 何が目 的だ ?
Oh my, the secret's out already?
ありやあ… もうバレちまつたか?
ん一 どういうつもりだ?
What are you trying to do?
お前は銃を向けたぐらいじや
ロを割らない夕イブのようだ
You don't seem to be the type to yield to a gun pointed at you,
so I'll perform some torture on you instead.
だから これから少し
拷問させてもらう
何だ そりや? 拷問だ?
Are you joking?
Torture, you say?
This isn't the middle ages, you know?
いつの時代の人間なんだ お前はよ ?
おいおい お前はありがたく
銃を捨てて<れたけどよ
Hey, hey. Even though you happily threw your gun away,
I still have one right—
こつちには こういう立派なもんが…
つて‥ あれ?
Eh?
うわつ うわああああ
改めて 聞 こ う !
Let me ask you again.
お前は誰だ!?
Who are you?
ああっ うつ…
残念だ
That's a shame.
つっ つつ つゎ つゎ'
うゎつ うゎつ くくく ぐあっ!
も う一度聞く お前は誰だ ?
I'll ask you again.
Who are you?
デユ デユ一… ンン…
D-Dune...
どこのデユ一ンだ?
And where are you from, Dune?
ぐゎあ うがあああああ
アハハ ハハ一 うおお~!
一体 こんなことしたのは
どんな奴なんだろうな!?
What kind of guy would do all this?!
It must be some unbelievably amazing guy!
さぞかしスゲ工奴なんだろうな !
すごすきて自分が殺されることなんて
者えたこともねえだろうなぁ !
He's so amazing he probably never even thinks about getting killed himself.
I mean, we...
つうか それ 俺だし…
俺 負けてらんねえし!
I can't lose to that!
Good friend of the Russo family, Dune-kun...
丿しツソフア三リ一の
お友達のデユ一ン君!
お前たちの計画は分かつ た
I understand your plans now.
I want to ask you one more thing.
もうー つ聞いていいか?
なぜ お前は車掌の格好をしてる?
Why are you wearing a conductor's uniform?
I give up, I give up!
気分‥ 気分‥
好きなんだ… うツ ドは…
He loves it, Ladd does!
To play! To kill!
遊ぴ! 殺しが!
I see.
なるほど 遊ぴ心つてわけか
So you like to play games?
じやあ その制服を どこで手に入れた ?
Where did you obtain your conductor's uniform?
今朝… 駅で… ジジイの車掌から
This morning, at the station, I got it from some old fart of a conductor.
そいつを… どうした?
What did you do with him?
I killed him!
殺した… 気分で… 遊ぴ… 遊ぴ!
I felt like it! Play! Play!
フへへ~ !
That conductor's name is Tony!
その車掌の名前は
卜二一つていうんだ
He's the man who told me all about being a conductor.
俺に車掌のイロハを
教えてくれた男だ
ひやあは~ うう はははは あははは…
Watch out.
気をつけろ
I have no clue what or who he is, but there's someone dangerous riding this train.
この列車には
何だか知らねえがヤバいのがいる
俺は これからそいつや黒服を
殺しに行くから隠れてろ
I'm going to kill him and the black-suits now, so hide, okay?
Okay.
忘れんな お前を殺すのは
この俺なんだからよ な?
Don't forget,
I will be the one to kill you, right?
Yes...
レムレ一スだ?
丿しツソファ三リ一だ? 笑わせるな
The Lemures...
The Russo family...
Don't make me laugh...
俺は お前ら に と つての怪物だ
I will be your monster!
A monster that will devour all of you!
お前らをすベて食らい尽くず怪物だ
今から俺は この列車に と つての
From now on, for this train, for you, I will be Rail Tracer!
お前らにとっての
レイ 丿し卜レ一サ一だ !
車掌 ?
Conductor?
車掌です
It was a conductor.
あれは車掌の制服を
着ていました
It was wearing a conductor's uniform.
で その化け物は
君に何と言つたのかね ?
And? What did that monster tell you?
切符を拝見…
Show me your ticket, please.
アツハツハツハツ…
失礼…
Excuse me.
あれは私が無賃乗車であることを
知つていたんだと思います
I think it knew I was taking a free ride.
なるほど…
やはり間違いないようだね
I see.
There's no mistaking it.
その車掌は… ヴイ一ノ だよ
That conductor is Vino.
なぜ その赤い怪物が
ヴイ一ノだと?
Why do you think that red monster is Vino?
ヴイ一ノは全米中の都市に現れる
神出鬼没の怪物として恐れられていた
Vino was feared as an elusive monster who appeared in cities throughout America.
事実 彼は予想もできない場所に
突如として現れ 去っていき
In reality, he would just suddenly appear in a certain place, then leave,
before turning up again in some other place.
さらにまた
予想もしない場所に現れる
How could he manage such a thing?
どうすれば そんなことが
可能になるのか?
もしヴイ一ノが大陸横断特急の
車掌だつたとしたら?
What if he was a conductor on board a transcontinental train?
神出鬼没の説明もつきます
His elusiveness could very well be explained.
それならば たいていの都市に
出没するのは当たり前のことだからね
Then it would be obvious why he would appear and disappear from cities all the time.
Vino...
ヴイ一ノ 聞いたことはあります
I have heard about him.
ヴイ一ノこと
クレアス夕ンフイ一ルドは
Vino, or Claire Stanfield, was raised by the father of the Gandor brothers.
ガン ド一ル兄弟の父親に育てられた
彼が孤児になつた時 隣に住んでいたのが
ガンド一ルだつたわけだ
When he became an orphan, the Gandors lived next door.
したカヾつて兄弟とは
家族同然の仲であり
As a result, he was as a brother to them and as such, part of the family.
実質的に4人目の兄弟といつても
差し支えない
And in reality, you could call him the fourth brother of the Gandors.
その後 サ一力スに
引き取られたそうですが…
I heard he was taken in by a circus afterwards, though?
そのとお り だ
That's right.
クレアはサ一力スで
超人的な才能と努力により
Thanks to his hard work and superhuman talent, he was able to obtain beyond-human strength and technique.
文字どおり人間を超えた体力と
技術を身につけることになつた
それが殺し屋となつた現在でも
役に立っているのだろう
That is probably also coming in handy now that he has become an assassin.
ダア一一 ノツノツノツノツノノノ
イ一一 ハツハツハツハツ…
Hey, can't you shut up for a bit?
おい 黙らねえか !
ヒヤア ハツハハ ハハハハ
I guess you and Ladd are satisfied if you can just kill...
お前やラッ ドの旦那は
殺しができりゃ満足なんだろうけどよ
こつちは先立つもんがなけ り や
But I have other priorities.
ううつ?
Vino's killing methods are famous for being filthy.
ヴイ 一 ノ の殺し方は汚いので有名だ
The bodies left from his killings are on the verge of complete destruction,
彼の手にかかった人間の体は
破壊の限りを尽くされる
まるでブドウ酒をぶちまけたように
as if they were drowned in red wine...
うゎあああぁ…
殺し屋として
完璧な仕事をするために
To fulfill his work as an assassin, he apparently can't be satisfied if he doesn't go that far.
そこまでやらないと
安心できないらしいのだ
ヴイ 一 ノ がガン ド一ル三兄弟 と
Were you able to confirm that Vino was in contact with the Gandor Brothers?
コン夕ク卜を取つたのは
確認できたのかね?
はい
Yes.
どうしたんだよ
そんなボロボロにな… ウプ!
What happened? You look like shit—
If you live long enough, I'll tell you sometime!
長い人生 そのうち話す時も来るさ ア !
It sure has been a long time!
失礼 ガン ド一ル様で
いらつしやいますか?
Excuse me. Are you Mr. Gandor?
Yes...
そうですが
これをお預かりしました
I was told to give this to you.
Thanks.
ありがとう
キ一兄
Keith.
クレアよお お前 車掌なのに
何でこんなとこに…
Hey, Claire!
Why are you in a place like this? You're one of the conductors, right?
俺はもうクレアじゃない
車掌でもない
I'm not Claire anymore, and I'm not a conductor either.
じやあ 何て呼べばいいんですか?
Then, what should we call you?
ま ヴイ一ノか…
レイ丿し卜レ一サ一とでも呼んでくれ
Well, Vino, or... you can call me Rail Tracer.
だつせえ
That's pathetic!
さて 行くか
まずは誰を殺せばいい?
Well then, shall we go?
Who do I have to kill?
こつちはゆうベ
I only got some light exercise last night, so I'm getting a little rusty.
軽い運動しかできな<て
体が謹つてるんだ
久々に本気を出せる仕事をしたい
I'm looking forward to a job where I have to use my all again.
ぱぱっと終わらせよう 俺はこのあと
人を捜さなきゃならないんだ
Let's get it over with.
After this, I have to look for someone.
It might just be someone who is going to marry me.
もしかしたら俺と
結婚して<れるかもしれない人だ
But why did he do it, I wonder?
しかし なぜなんでしよう?
ヴイ一ノはなぜ あんな無差別殺人を
行ったんでしようか?
Why did he commit all those indiscriminate murders?
謹から無差別に見えても
Even though they might have looked indiscriminate on the surface,
彼の中では
ある倫理に基ついた行動なのだろう
they were probably based on a sense of ethics he holds.
ヴイ一ノがやや ゆがんだ正義感の
持ち主であるらしいことは
It has been reported that Vino has, though it's somewhat warped, a sense of justice.
以前から報告されている
しかし あんな年端のいかない
子供まで…
But he even killed a child...
それは どのような子供かね ?
And what kind of child was that?
ー0歳くらいの男の子なんですが…
A child around ten years old...
なるほど…
I see. Then you can probably ask him yourself sometime.
それはいずれ その子本人に
尋ねてみたらいいんじゃないかね
本人? 本人つて…
"Him yourself?" By that you mean?
さて レイチ工ル君
Well now, Rachel-kun. There are still loads of things I want to ask you.
まだまだ聞いておかなければ
ならないことは 山ほどある
君のその ケガのことも
まだ話してもらっていないレね
You still haven't told me how you got that injury either.
はい…
Yes...
何だ ?
What's this?
こいつは一体…
What's going on?
ダラスよお
Dallas...
あの女 俺たちに
何か注射しや力ヾったんだ
That woman injected us with something...
お目覚めのようだな
I see you're awake.
誰だ てめえ…
俺たちをどうする気だ
Who are you, bastard?!
What do you want with us?!
私はセラ一 ドク工一ツ
I am Szilard Quates.
君たちには聞きたいことを聞いてから
死んでもらうつもりだ
I'm planning to kill you after you tell me what I need to know.
満足かね
Satisfied with that?
Kill us, you say?!
死んでもらうだと?
てめえ やれるもんなら…
Just try and—
Hey! Hey! Hey!
おい おい おい!
ふん ロクな生き方は
しておらんな…
I see you haven't done much good in your lives.
ほう‥
Hmm, I can't tell whether the elixir is all right or not, but...
薬は…
無事かどうか分からんな
ダラスジ工ノア一ド
Dallas Genoard!
Would you care to make a deal with me?
取引をする気はないか
ふん… シヨックカヾ豆菫すきたようだ
続きは あとだな
I see the shock is too strong.
We'll continue later.
工二ス… その場にいた
あとの2人はどうした?
Ennis, what happened to the other two who were there?
Eh? It seems they left soon after.
すぐ その場を離れたようです
尾行された形跡はありません
There were no traces of me being followed.
そうか… なら問題はあるまい
I see. Then there's no problem.
はい
Yes.
It seems the complete product is at the headquarters of a mafia family called the Gandors.
完成品はガンド一ルとかいう
マフイアのアジ卜にあるようだ
下手に交渉して こちらの情報を
与えるのもマズい
If we were to negotiate and if our information were leaked to them, that'd be bad.
あの3人に奪い取つてこさせろ
Let those three go and get it.
連中 ガン ド一ルに恨みもあるら しい
Apparently they harbor a certain hate for the Gandors.
自分たちが不死身の体になつたと知れば
喜んで従うだろう
Since they have obtained immortal bodies now, they'll obey happily, I think.
はい
Yes.
Master Szilard!
セう一 ド様 !
や やはり先ほどの注射は…
未完成品であっても あの…
What you did just now, even though it was an incomplete product...
Why did you give it those—
なぜあんな低俗な連中に…
Shut up!
うるさい !
マフ イアとケン力になるかもしれん
We might get into a fight with the mafia.
They are our tools to help with that.
あの連中は そのための道具だ
用が済んだら食う
文句があるか?
When that's done, I'll "eat" them!
Any problems with that?
If you have the strength to fight with the gangs and win, I can let you go instead, if you want.
お前らにギャングとつぶレあって
勝てるほどの体力があれば別だがな
キヤア
Mary!
メリ一!
ママあ
Mama!
ご安心 頂けましたかな?
Are you at ease now?
あの忌まわしい白服どもから ご令嬢を
救つて差し上げたのですからなぁ
We saved your daughter from those disgusting white-suited people after all.
さて明朝 この列車が通過する橋の上に
鶏ろ慄が上がつていれば
Well then, if there's a beacon light on top of the bridge the train is passing tomorrow morning,
とりあえず
あなたたちは助かります
you will be safe for the time being.
と り あえず ですがね
For the time being, mind you.
We're negotiating.
交渉ですよ
列車内からは
交渉できませんので
Since I can't negotiate from the train, I'm letting others negotiate with your husband.
配下の者に あなたのご主人と
交渉させているのです
そんな‥
No way...
If we can't get your husband to understand the deal,
in order to make him understand it's no empty threat,
もし ご主人に
理解 頂けなかつた場合には
我々の行為が脅しではないと
分かつて頂くために
お嬢さんの死体を線路に
置き去りにすることになりますので
we will leave your daughter's body on the rails, so...
please bear with us.
どうか ご了承下さい
代わりに私を殺せなどと
おっしゃらないで頂きたいですな
I would like you to avoid saying to kill you instead of the girl...
理由は特にありませんが
面倒なので却下と言つておきます
We don't really have a reason, but since it's bothersome, I'll have to refuse in such a case.
それと線路の途中で
警察の妨害などが みられた場合にも
Or if the police have barricaded the railroad, we will kill her as well,
お子さんがてくなることになりますので
ご承知置きを
so please understand.
As a final bit of information, we will kill her with guns, so please prepare yourself.
参者までに申し上げておきますと
銃殺ですので ご覚悟下さい
レイズ
I raise.
おいおい 強気じゃねえか
Pretty bold move!
俺はおりるぜ
I fold.
Then I call.
じや こつちはコ一ルといくか
何だ てめえら
Who are you guys?
えぇ いえ 実は昼間 こちらに
忘れ物をしてしまいまして…
Ahh, no, we just forgot something here this afternoon.
忘れ物だぁ ?
Forgot something?!
はい あ~ あの箱です
Yes, it's that box!
悪いけどなあ あれが本当に
あんたらのかどうか 分からねえからよ…
I'm sorry, but since we can't tell whether that's really yours or not,
日月巳 ラックさんが来るまで
待つてくれ… えっ?
can you wait until Mr. Luck comes back tomorrow—
この程度かよ おい !
What weaklings!
人を さんざん
クズ呼ばわりしや力ヾつて…
To think they went around and called us trash!
それで これかよ!
ありがたくて笑つちまうぜ おい!
And then they go down like this?!
I just can't help but laugh!
Telephone...
電話… ラツクさんに… 連絡を…
I have to... call... Mr. Luck...
はぁ… はあ…
ラツクさんたちは… 確か‥
I thought... Mr. Luck was...
痛かつたぜ
That hurt!
あっ あっ あっ ああ'
ホン 卜に不死身なんだなぁ !
We're really immortal!
I'm moved.
感動だぁ…
あぁ まつたく感動だよ!
I'm so moved!
ブ~~ン ブ~ン
用つて何だ ガキ?
So what did you want to talk about, brat?
お兄ちやんつて
すつごく強いんだね!
You're very strong, aren't you?!
僕 ぴつくりしちやつた !
I was surprised!
ほ一 そ
う力 ? そつ思うか?
Oh, I see.
You think so?
Yeah!
うん! お兄ちゃんが
リングに上がつてたら
If you got up in the ring, you'd definitely be wearing the champion's belt now!
絶対に今頃 べル卜を
巻いてるよね !
お世辞のうまいガキは嫌いじやねえ
I like kids who are good at complimenting.
で 何の用だ?
So, what did you want?
実はね お兄ちゃんに
お願いがあるの
Actually, I have a request for you.
お願いだあ ?
Request, you say?
ふあ… そんな怖い顔しないでよ
お兄ちゃん
Don't make such a scary face, please.
うるせえ
てめえは今年25になる
Shut up.
Don't forget the only reason you're still alive is because you don't call me, who has just turned 25, an old man.
このラツ ド様を
オジサン呼ばわりしなかつただけで
生きながらえてる命だつてことを
忘れるな
お前が言う お願いとやらが
俺を怒らせるガ笑わせるかで
Depending on your request, whether I will laugh or get angry, that will decide your lifespan, boy.
お前の寿命が決まるぞ ボウズ
あのね あのね 食堂車の人たちを…
So, so... Can't you kill all the people in the dining car for me?
皆殺しにしてくれないかな?
何?
What?
お前 自分の言ってることが
分かつてんのか?
Do you understand what you're saying?
Yeah.
dokomade mo tsuzuiteru hoshizora miagete utau
I sing, looking up into the endless starry night.
kagiriaru bokutachi no eien wo yume miru melody
A melody in a dream... about our limited eternity.
mune ni afureru itoshisa no mizu wa
This water of love, overflowing from my chest...
mirai no hate de dareka ni todoku darou
I wonder if it will reach someone in the future?
shinjite iruyo
I will believe in you.
harukana toki wo kake nukete
Transcending generations of time...
bokutachi no yobigoe wa itsuka ookina uta ni naru
Will our calls turn into a beautiful song one day?
ai wo tsumuide yukeru yo
You can start building your love,
ima wa mada konnani chiisana hikari dakedo
Though right now, the light is still faint.
Next ep
Preview
Czeslaw Meyer is Forced to Rework
His Tremble-Before-the-Specter-of-Immortals Strategy
Hey, Miria, I wonder what Czes-kun is so afraid of.
The sha (person) in fushisha (immortal person) means human, right?
And what does fushi (immortal) mean?
It must be the fushi from fushidara (immoral).
So he's afraid of an immoral person!
That's no surprise!
On top of that, it's his shadow!